## SIRICHAI JANPAN

### Programmer at Ascendcorp

DATE OF BIRTH: February 18th 1995 (25 years old)

EMAIL: - HIDDEN -

PHONE: - HIDDEN -



Hi, I'm a Junior Developer with 3 year experience with PHP, Javascript, Laravel, Nodejs, Angular and React(Beginner). In the current company, I did many projects not only backend but also frontend and fullstack and now I seeking for new job to develop my programmer language skills.

#### SKILL SET

PHP: 3 years REST API: 3 years

Node.js: 1 year Laravel: 3 years

CSS: 2 years AJAX: 3 years

JQuery: 3 years Javascript: 3 years

MySQL: 3 years phpci: 3 years

AngularJS: 3 years React: 3 years

Model-View-Controller (MVC): 3 years

### WORK EXPERIENCE

Ascendcorp • Sep 2018 - Present

Programmer 1 year 8 months

- Have an experience in development Microservice
- Have an experience in Rest-full Api
- Have an experience in Laravel , Lumen , Nodejs (express).
- Have an experience in Docker and Git

Nilecon • Jun 2017 - Jul 2018

Web developer 1 year 1 month

- Have an experience in development Project Todobox (Front-end by Angular1 + Section API & Back-end by laravel framework)



- Have an experience in development Project Baby Best Buy (Section API & Back-end by laravel framework)
- Have an experience in development Project Beauty24 (Front-end by html + jquery,ajax)

# **EDUCATION**

Prince of Songkla University

2013 - 2017

ICM

Bachelor

# LANGUAGES

English: Intermediate

Thai : Native

